Spot the excellent elementary school student, Hyogo!
Good boy!
Whoo!
Well, you know, in elementary school, it said Hyogo.
What's Hyogo?
Traffic safety
It's written on it, right?
Liquid...
Is there a gold prize?
Ukisho: No.
Kyomoto, I only have a provisional work.
Nasu, seriously?
Ukisho No, seriously.
Nasu No, that's not it.
Nasu: Well, it's called a provisional work.
Fujisho: Like a successor.
Ukisho Well, I...
Ukisho, I won a gold prize for a picture of toothpaste.
Ohmitsu
Nasu There are many things like that, aren't there?
Omitsu That's interesting.
Nasu So, um...
Nasu I'm going to ask you to submit the problems in order.
Nasu I will select the various vote numbers.
Rakurageki Yes.
Nasu And one more thing, I have to look at the vote number.
Nasu From those three numbers
Nasu Which one is the vote number of the elementary school student?
Ukisho: You two can confuse them.
Ukisho: We just have to guess.
Nasu Right.
Ukisho...
Nasu, just guess.
Ukisho. But it's easy.
Nasu Yeah.
Ukisho, you're right.
Ukisho, you can do it now, can't you?
Nasu But this time, it's a penalty game.
Ukisho: What? Is there?
Ukisho: A penalty game?
Nasu: Is there?
Ukisho, I hate it so much.
Ukisho, hey, that's us.
Ukisho, you're the hardest worker today.
Ukisho, one week.
Ukisho's insta-story
Ukisho, the vote number is accurate!
Ukisho, you're in trouble!
Nasu Oh no!
Nasu, what's that?
Ukisho What?
Nasu But, you know, you can't lose to Shun-chan, can you? I'm actually...
Ukisho I got all the answers right.
Ukisho: Oh, my God,
Nasu That's right.
Nasu Just the number of insta-stories.
Nasu I'll do it for a day.
Ukisho I'll do it all.
Ukisho I'll totally do it.
Nasu, let's go.
Ukisho I won't lose!
Ukisho, I'll do my best!
Nasu, yes!
Ukisho, the theme is traffic safety.
Nasu Yes, sir!
Ukisho, A.
Ukisho, don't jump out of the way
Ukisho You are everyone's treasure
Nasu That's a good vote.
Nasu Even I find it hard to criticize.
Ukisho B
Ukisho: If the signal was shiny
Ukisho: Patience, patience, patience.
Nasu, that's so annoying!
Nasu, that's good!
Ukisho C
Ukisho, give me your hand instead of mom's to hold the baggage.
Ukisho, that's too hard!
Ukisho, that's too much!
Nasu, you're so good!
Ukisho: I'll put my hand up instead of Mom holding the luggage.Ukisho raises his hand in place of Mom holding the luggage
Ukisho raises his B
Ukisho: Beautiful!
Nasu: So, so bad,
Ukisho No, wait, wait!
Ukisho, wait!
Nasu, you're too shiny.
Ukisho, wait a minute.
Ukisho, by the way, you're in the first grade of elementary school.
Ukisho, what?
Nasu, definitely a first grader.
Ukisho: Is this verification a treasure?
Nasu, if that's the case, if it's really a "C"...
Nasu, make a big face. I've got your back.
Nasu I don't think it's a super 1.
Ukisho Well, well, well.
Nasu I see.
Nasu Okay, then.
Ukisho, yes.
Nasu, let's get ready.
Nasu, ready?
Ukisho A.
Ukisho A
Ukisho C.
Ukisho. Wow! You did it!
Ukisho: Well, that's definitely a C.
Nasu C, right?
Nasu Yeah.
Nasu I'm on the side of the judges now.
Ukisho: Yeah, I'm on the jury side, too.
Ukisho: I think people write words like "treasure" a lot.
Nasu Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ukisho: Yeah, yeah.
Nasu As expected, there were some mottoes that showed the limit of our knowledge.
Nasu It's a feeling that these are everyone's treasures.
Ukisho That's cute, isn't it?
Nasu I thought that was the biggest answer that came out of it.
Nasu I thought it was cute, and that was A.
Nasu The rest were not so cute.
Ukisho B
Ukisho I don't think there's any B.
Nasu B! Isn't that bad?
Ukisho: Considering it's been a year, I think C is pretty.
Ukisho, B is just a joke by Shimeshima-chan...
Ukisho: Well, I think it's A.
Ukisho, please.
Nasu: Correct! Definitely C.
Ukisho, this is really big.
Nasu: The correct answer is
Nasu The correct answer is A!
Nasu Whose work is C?
Nasu C is for Mr. Sasak.
Wow!
As expected, too cool!
Nasu C, wow!
That's what I meant.
Nasu C is good!
Nasu C. I think it's great!
Nasu You should write lyrics!
Nasu Seriously!
Nasu I'm in the first grade of elementary school
Nasu I can't do it, I'm going to get a reaction out of you.
Nasu D. Shunta
Nasu No, I'm not kidding.
Nasu, why don't you get it!
Nasu Why don't you get it!
Nasu, C is for information and morals.
Nasu What's that?
Nasu What's that, information morality?
Nasu A!
Nasu I'd rather say it directly than like it.
Nasu Yum!
Nasu I'm sure it's good!
Nasu, that's really nice.
Nasu, うまー!
Nasu B!
Nasu I started a social networking site to find out more about her.
Nasu Yeah.
Nasu That's not quite right.
Nasu I'm scared, scared
Nasu I'm differentNasu I don't.
Nasu I saw this, I saw this.
Nasu C!
Nasu I value family time more than games
Nasu Hmmm...
Nasu So, what is it? What year is this? Elementary school student?
Nasu This is, I think, the upper grades of elementary school, right?
Nasu Okay, okay.
Nasu Shall we go?
Nasu, yes.
Nasu, I'm going.
Nasu, ready!
Nasu, B!
Nasu C!
Nasu A!
Nasu, wow!
Nasu, you're right!
Nasu What the hell!
Nasu That's right!
Nasu I'm just this elementary school kid.
Nasu Just cut something current for now.
Nasu I thought there might be a theory that Hyogo was in there.
Nasu That's me!
Nasu I'm already a pure fan of this person, too.
Nasu It's really good!
Nasu This is...
Nasu The correct answer is!
They are all shhh!
Kanya Yoshizawa OP
Nyoru Matsukura, option
Ryuga Matsukura, stratery
Subtitle for Matsukura
Kanya Yoshizawa, Nakamura Matsuda
Tsurime Life
Jesse female
Kaito Miyachika
Miyachika Jesse
, knee
Motoki
Fumishi Yasujima
Shintaro
Captain for a while
You guys couldn't edit it.
Thanks, I liked that one.
I got it!
Basics especially
A. How can you give up so easily?
B.Festival, make noise, in my heart
C.Bonding and smiling
Let's make it the best type of memorable, where everyone is the star
No, don't hesitate.
No, not this one.
I think B.
I think it's a B.
I think we're here.
Wait a minute.
Let's make some noise.
It's a festival. Make some noise.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's a Corona.
It's too good.
You know what I'm talking about.
I'm sure it is.
Okay, let's see what you got.
Okay.
C.B.C.
It's done.
There's no one here.
Me A, I practice.
Me B is too juvenile.
Correct.
C. Mush.
Mush is bad.
I fucked up.
Oh, man.
Who's B, by the way?
Too obvious.
Let's move on to the next theme.
The theme is "Cultural Festival.
Festival.Cultural Festival.
A. Best cultural festival
B.Favorite season ranking No.1 Autumn
A. Best festival
I know, I know, I know.
This is what I'm talking about.
It's so hard!
C. Screw you.
You gotta be kidding me.
What? What? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're kidding me. I'm kidding you.
Huh?
Oh, my God.
What the hell?
Three.
That's funny, that's funny, that's funny, that's funny.
I don't think there's a "B" in there.
What was that?
What does that mean?
That's why we're not allowed to fool around.
School.
But we're allowed to joke around with the best of them.
Oh, I see what you mean.
That's so cool!
Okay.
Now?
A.
Aaaaah!
This is it.
I'm gonna make you do it.
The answer is
A.
Yay!
It's Shun Tan!
Yes!
The 1st is decided?
The 1st is decided.
Now you know.
What's the score so far?
Three.
Two.
Four.
1 point
One.
So KAN-chan is confirmed?
Okay, then.
I'm counting on you.
Do something for me.
Well, well, well...
Package.
Rust.
Yes, please!
Hard is the law!
Here you go, toothpaste!
Here we go.
Let's see.
The correct answer is...
8,000.
Woooo...
Seriously?
Kan-chan's in trouble.
I don't mind.
Nothing.
I'm bringing B's along, just to be here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Here we go.
A.
Dentist.
Is he really nice?
Do you know?
Yes, I do.
A.
Is he really nice?
Yes, I know.
She's cute.So cute!
Cute. Cute. Cute.
I see.
Cute.
B
Brush your teeth.
You smile.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
If you brush your teeth
Brush your teeth
They're so dirty
And you're smiling
I'm a puri, right?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
You did it!
Oh, no.
Shhh.
You've got to be kidding me.
Grandpa
Shiny when you smile
Teeth and head
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Wait a minute
Ew.
Ah.
This one.
This is difficult
This is hard!
Surprisingly
In the countryside.
There are advertisements.
Yes, there are.
It's not so bad.
It's a little annoying.
Shall we go?
I'm in.
I'll answer.
Yes, sir.
Ready?
A.
It's a piece of shit, right?
B
Shhh.
Ew.
You're right, at first I thought you were kidding with the schooner.
I thought you might be.
It's pretty much on the side.
It's like it's right next to the ad.
I know, right?
Or maybe it's on your head.
Oh...
It's right along with the picture.
Yes, yes, yes.
Is that your final answer?
Yes.
Yes, that's definitely the final answer.
The correct answer is
Reina, Se-no.
Jude
Overlap the spirit
That's it!
Leader
Jal
zero
oe
Wow, I did it!
Oh no, I'll never make it.
Good for you.
It's definitely over.
Well, it starts today, so...
What?
From the time this went up.
Oh, right.Oh, yeah.
You know the theme of the day, right?
The one we did today.
About milk.
About milk
With the market price
Oh, OK, OK.
Maybe with a picture.
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Yes, I mean...
That's all for the milk.
Thank you so much!
It was a lot of fun.